<resources>
    <string name="app_name">FLY</string>
    <string name="play">Play</string>
    <string name="pause">Pause</string>
    <string name="name">Name</string>
    <string name="email">Email</string>
    <string name="username">Username</string>
    <string name="password">Password</string>
    <string name="register">Register</string>
    <string name="date_of_birth">DOB</string>
    <string name="reenterpassword">Re-Enter Password</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="palawan">"Voted the world's most beautiful island more than once, Palawan is a slice of heaven, teeming with exotic wildlife, quaint fishing villages, and UNESCO World Heritage Sites. Visit the Calauit Game Preserve and Wildlife Sanctuary or explore the Japanese shipwrecks of Coron Island, regarded as one of the best dive sites in the world."</string>
    <string name="moraine">"Moraine Lake may only only half the size of its nearby neighbour Lake Louise, but it's even more scenic. Situated in the beautiful Valley Of The Ten Peaks in Banff National Park, this glacier-fed lake turns the most intense and vivid shade of turquoise blue. The setting of the surrounding majestic mountain peaks makes the scene almost surreal."</string>
    <string name="cliffs">"These soaring cliffs in County Clare are one of Ireland's most famous tourist attractions. The maximum height of Cliffs is 214 m. This natural sanctuary is home to some 30,000 birds from 20 different species."</string>
    <string name="great">"Diverse aquatic species include leatherback turtles and clown fish, the Great Barrier Reef needs no introduction. The world's largest coral reef system composed of over 2,900 individual reefs and 900 islands stretching for over 2,300 kilometres over an area of approximately 344,400 square kilometres (133,000 sq mi), the Great Barrier Reef can be seen from outer space and is the world's biggest single structure made by living organisms."</string>
    <string name="iguazu">"One of the modern natural wonders of the world, this chain of mini waterfalls is one of the planet's most awe-inspiring sights. A visit is an awe-inspiring visceral experience, and the power and noise of the cascades – a chain of hundreds of waterfalls nearly 3km in extension – is something you won't forget. The falls lie split between Brazil and Argentina in a large expanse of national park, much of it rainforest teeming with unique flora and fauna."</string>
    <string name="valley">"Nestled in the Nanda Devi Biosphere, the Valley of Flowers is the most attractive place in Uttarakhand. Every inch of this place is blessed with unparalleled natural beauty in the form of endemic alpine flowers and diversity of flora, including medicinal herbs. Besides, it is also home to a variety of endangered species of animals, including the snow leopard, Asiatic black bear, blue sheep and musk deer, to name a few. Also, there are a host of gushing waterfalls and streams in this scenic valley. You need to trek to this beautiful valley, so be aware that July to September is the only time when trekking is allowed here."</string>
    <string name="dzukou">"Sandwiched between north-eastern states of Manipur and Nagaland, Dzukou Valley is home to lush green forest, mosaic of grasslands, flowers of varying hues, and an abundance of flora and fauna, making it a perfect spot to spend some time in the lap of Mother Nature. The Japfu hills add to the splendour of the place and make it is a perfect spot for trekking. If you’re not up for trekking, take a stroll among the ubiquitous flowers. This is home to a variety of flowers, including the rare and unique Dzükou lily, multi-colored rhododendrons and aconitum. The best time to visit is October to May. To reach the valley, you need to trek either from Zakhama village or Visvema village. Indian visitors need an inner line permit for Nagaland and foreign visitors must register themselves at the local state government office in Kohima or Dimapur, Nagaland."</string>
    <string name="pithoragarh">"Located in the eastern district of Uttarakhand, Pithoragarh boasts of irresistible natural beauty, high altitude grasslands and historic charm. It is the starting point for treks to the holy shrines of Kailash and Mansarovar. And, the panoramic views of the mighty peaks of Nanda Devi, Appi of Nepal and Panchachuli are clearly visible from this place. Some of the tourist spots include the Pithoragarh Fort, Askot Sanctuary that is home to a wide range of flora and fauna, and Kafni Glacier Trek, among many others. And, visitors can also indulge in adventure activities, like hiking, skiing, canoeing, kayaking and fishing. This tiny place is an ideal place for those looking for a nature retreat."</string>
    <string name="munnar">"Spend some “me” time in nature’s lap in Munnar, a hill station famous for its tea and spice plantations. Camping, parasailing, birdwatching, trekking, wildlife spotting, fishing, boating and rock climbing are the popular activities here. Some of the must-visit attractions include Echo Point, and Kundala Lake where you can enjoy boating and shikara rides amidst the natural beauty and views of rolling hills; Devikulum is home to an assortment of temples, Attakud waterfall and Anamudi Peak, among many others. For tea lovers, there’s a Tata Tea Museum where you can learn about the history of tea and its processing."</string>
    <string name="chail">"Sitting amid the Shivalik hills, Chail is a peaceful and secluded hill station that once served as a summer retreat for the Maharaja of Patiala. Surrounded by deodar and pine forests and replete with spectacular views of the mountains, this place is a delight for nature lovers and photographers. A visit to Sadhupul lake, Chail Palace, Kali temple and the Chail Wildlife Sanctuary is a must when in Chail."</string>

    <string name="mypara">"As we know that the stress has increased in our society, which leads to many severe health problems like Heart disease, Obesity, Depression and anxiety. This is also the main reason for attempting suicides. Therefore, We are making android app and website (www.firstloveyourself.co.in) that will motivate and guide people to live a stress free life. Our Application will contain the following features:
•         Motivational and Humorous  Contents (Videos, Articles): This will contain the videos and Articles of real life stories that can help to motivate the peoples. It will also contain some Humorous content too.
•         Chat: In this feature users can chat and share their problems with each other.
•         Counselors: This feature will help the peoples to chat with Counselors and if they like them then they can set an appointment.(COMING SOON…)
•         Explore The Nature: In this feature we will show the peoples the nature’s best place to visit so they can see how beautiful the life and nature is.
•         Events: This feature will contain all the lively events so where they can book the event and enjoy it.

This is the Pre-Beta version of our original work and we would be glad for your feedbacks(Can send as many you like).
                            THANK YOU!!!
"</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="the_worthy">The Worthy</string>
    <string name="loss">Loss</string>
    <string name="lets_go">Lets Go</string>
    <string name="legacy">Legacy</string>
    <string name="made_for_this">Made For This</string>
    <string name="you_will_never_be_a_god">You Will Never Be A God</string>
    <string name="how_to_stop_bullying">How To Stop Bullying</string>
    <string name="a_man_out_of_time">A Man Out Of Time</string>
    <string name="there_was_no_other_way">There Was No Other Way</string>
    <string name="humorous_1">Humorous 1</string>
    <string name="humorous_2">Humorous 2</string>
    <string name="humorous_3">Humorous 3</string>
    <string name="login">Login</string>
    <string name="enter_username">Enter Username</string>
    <string name="enter_password">Enter Password</string>
    <string name="title_activity_videos">videos</string>
    <string name="tab_text_1">Tab 1</string>
    <string name="tab_text_2">Tab 2</string>
    <string name="select_city">Please select your city</string>
    <string name="more_details">More Details</string>
    <string name="cuaz_it_matters">Cuaz It Matters...</string>
</resources>

