<resources>
    <string name="app_name">FLY</string>
    <string name="play">Play</string>
    <string name="pause">Pause</string>
    <string name="name">Name</string>
    <string name="email">Email</string>
    <string name="username">Username</string>
    <string name="password">Password</string>
    <string name="register">Register</string>
    <string name="date_of_birth">DOB</string>
    <string name="reenterpassword">Re-Enter Password</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="palawan">"Voted the world's most beautiful island more than once, Palawan is a slice of heaven, teeming with exotic wildlife, quaint fishing villages, and UNESCO World Heritage Sites. Visit the Calauit Game Preserve and Wildlife Sanctuary or explore the Japanese shipwrecks of Coron Island, regarded as one of the best dive sites in the world."</string>
    <string name="moraine">"Moraine Lake may only only half the size of its nearby neighbour Lake Louise, but it's even more scenic. Situated in the beautiful Valley Of The Ten Peaks in Banff National Park, this glacier-fed lake turns the most intense and vivid shade of turquoise blue. The setting of the surrounding majestic mountain peaks makes the scene almost surreal."</string>
    <string name="cliffs">"These soaring cliffs in County Clare are one of Ireland's most famous tourist attractions. The maximum height of Cliffs is 214 m. This natural sanctuary is home to some 30,000 birds from 20 different species."</string>
    <string name="great">"Diverse aquatic species include leatherback turtles and clown fish, the Great Barrier Reef needs no introduction. The world's largest coral reef system composed of over 2,900 individual reefs and 900 islands stretching for over 2,300 kilometres over an area of approximately 344,400 square kilometres (133,000 sq mi), the Great Barrier Reef can be seen from outer space and is the world's biggest single structure made by living organisms."</string>
    <string name="iguazu">"One of the modern natural wonders of the world, this chain of mini waterfalls is one of the planet's most awe-inspiring sights. A visit is an awe-inspiring visceral experience, and the power and noise of the cascades – a chain of hundreds of waterfalls nearly 3km in extension – is something you won't forget. The falls lie split between Brazil and Argentina in a large expanse of national park, much of it rainforest teeming with unique flora and fauna."</string>
    <string name="valley">"Nestled in the Nanda Devi Biosphere, the Valley of Flowers is the most attractive place in Uttarakhand. Every inch of this place is blessed with unparalleled natural beauty in the form of endemic alpine flowers and diversity of flora, including medicinal herbs. Besides, it is also home to a variety of endangered species of animals, including the snow leopard, Asiatic black bear, blue sheep and musk deer, to name a few. Also, there are a host of gushing waterfalls and streams in this scenic valley. You need to trek to this beautiful valley, so be aware that July to September is the only time when trekking is allowed here."</string>
    <string name="dzukou">"Sandwiched between north-eastern states of Manipur and Nagaland, Dzukou Valley is home to lush green forest, mosaic of grasslands, flowers of varying hues, and an abundance of flora and fauna, making it a perfect spot to spend some time in the lap of Mother Nature. The Japfu hills add to the splendour of the place and make it is a perfect spot for trekking. If you’re not up for trekking, take a stroll among the ubiquitous flowers. This is home to a variety of flowers, including the rare and unique Dzükou lily, multi-colored rhododendrons and aconitum. The best time to visit is October to May. To reach the valley, you need to trek either from Zakhama village or Visvema village. Indian visitors need an inner line permit for Nagaland and foreign visitors must register themselves at the local state government office in Kohima or Dimapur, Nagaland."</string>
    <string name="pithoragarh">"Located in the eastern district of Uttarakhand, Pithoragarh boasts of irresistible natural beauty, high altitude grasslands and historic charm. It is the starting point for treks to the holy shrines of Kailash and Mansarovar. And, the panoramic views of the mighty peaks of Nanda Devi, Appi of Nepal and Panchachuli are clearly visible from this place. Some of the tourist spots include the Pithoragarh Fort, Askot Sanctuary that is home to a wide range of flora and fauna, and Kafni Glacier Trek, among many others. And, visitors can also indulge in adventure activities, like hiking, skiing, canoeing, kayaking and fishing. This tiny place is an ideal place for those looking for a nature retreat."</string>
    <string name="munnar">"Spend some “me” time in nature’s lap in Munnar, a hill station famous for its tea and spice plantations. Camping, parasailing, birdwatching, trekking, wildlife spotting, fishing, boating and rock climbing are the popular activities here. Some of the must-visit attractions include Echo Point, and Kundala Lake where you can enjoy boating and shikara rides amidst the natural beauty and views of rolling hills; Devikulum is home to an assortment of temples, Attakud waterfall and Anamudi Peak, among many others. For tea lovers, there’s a Tata Tea Museum where you can learn about the history of tea and its processing."</string>
    <string name="chail">"Sitting amid the Shivalik hills, Chail is a peaceful and secluded hill station that once served as a summer retreat for the Maharaja of Patiala. Surrounded by deodar and pine forests and replete with spectacular views of the mountains, this place is a delight for nature lovers and photographers. A visit to Sadhupul lake, Chail Palace, Kali temple and the Chail Wildlife Sanctuary is a must when in Chail."</string>

    <string name="article1">"You can be hindered from making progress if you ignore your problems. Could you be letting little challenges grow into huge obstacles by not dealing with them?
When faced with unpleasant situations it is tempting to ignore them and not deal with them. The path of least resistance is an attractive one and the effort required to deal with the problem sometimes seems too immense. At times it’s not so much that the problem is big but that it requires us to admit something about ourselves or others that we just don’t want to face. The trouble is “You will not find a solution by saying there is no problem.”
 the dangers of not handling your problems
The longer you take to deal with your problems the bigger they will grow and the harder it will be to sort them out. They are like weeds that grow in a beautiful garden. If not recognized and uprooted early enough they will dominate the garden and choke the beautiful flowers in the garden. In fact you will forget there was ever a lovely garden there to begin with.
Secondly, when ignored, problems may become accepted as the norm. I remember working at a hospital where there are often shortages of medical supplies. As medical staff there we got so used to improvising that even when some supplies were in stock we did not think of using them. For instance, we improvised arm slings for shoulder dislocations and broken limbs by using bandages and empty fluid bags. One nurse actually had to remind me that the pharmacy had plenty of arm slings so I should not be wasting people’s money by telling them to buy bandages instead. My mind had become accustomed to the abnormal to such an extent that it became normal and I absolutely did not think there was any other way to get the job done.
There are many abnormal situations and circumstances in our lives that we have become used to and comfortable with to the extent that we do not see the need for change. It is possible for you to become used to poverty and lack. It is even possible to get used to mediocrity and failure. Ignore the problem long enough and it may no longer become a problem to you. The trouble is you will not be living the kind of life you should be living. “Making do” is not always a good thing.

Lastly, a problem that is not dealt with can lead to other problems. Unfortunately, problems are very social creatures and they will eagerly invite other problems into your life if you harbour them for too long. By not controlling one you may be opening the door to many others. It’s the domino effect: one action or lack of it in this case, can lead to many different consequences.
 change your thinking
So how do you deal with problems? The first and best way is to change the way you think about problems. . “The way you see the problem is the problem.” I like to think of such things as “challenges” rather than problems because “Problem” is a dead-end word. It leaves no room for solutions. When you regard something as a challenge instead, it leaves your mind free to think about how to respond to it. If you see it as a temporary obstacle you are more likely to feel empowered and able to deal with it.
David Oyedepo and Chris Oyakhilome, who are both pastors, say that many people have asked them whether they ever have problems in their lives as they always seem to be having it easy and things are always working out for them. Their response is that they don’t remember having problems. They add that perhaps the problem came, but they did not recognize it. Their mindset is one of dealing with things as they come and knowing that they have the answer to anything that they face. As they are on God’s side, I’m sure they cannot fail to have answers.
focus on the desired outcome
A second way to deal with a problem is to focus on the solution instead. Focusing on the problem too much may actually make it more impossible to solve. This can make the problem so big in your mind that it obscures or overshadows any possible solution. Try instead to think about what life would be like if the problem were solved. This brings your creativity into play and your mind will soon find ways to solve the problem.
According to Albert Einstein “You can't solve a problem with the same kind of thinking that created it.” A third way to deal with problems, then, is to alter your viewpoint. One way of doing this is to distance yourself emotionally from the problem. Try looking at the problem as an impartial observer and not as someone actively involved in it. This technique will not only make the problem seem less daunting, but will also help you to find possible solutions. When you are emotionally involved in something it clouds your judgment and dulls your creativity.
have a sense of humour
Finally, “laugh at your problems; everybody else does.” It is important to realise that any problem, no matter how big it may seem at the time, has a solution and is usually not the end of our lives as we may often feel. As long as you are breathing no problem is beyond solving. There is always hope to those that will look for it. Take life in your stride. Do not get bogged down by it and don’t ever forget to enjoy it. A free and fun mindset alone will go a long way in helping you to deal with your problems.
 the conclusion
Look ahead with confidence. Stay focused on what you want and not what’s in your way. “Don't be pushed by your problems. Be led by your dreams.”
You are all you can be. Go on and be it.
LINK: https://www.motivation-for-dreamers.com/dealing-with-problems.html"
</string>
    <string name="article2">
"Are you discouraged whenever you come across a little opposition and resistance? Do you fail to achieve your dreams because you always expect and want it to be easy to do so?
Whatever you want to achieve in life, it is very likely that you will run into some resistance. This resistance may come in various forms and at times from unexpected or unusual places.
the laws of nature
It is a natural thing in nature that for every action there is an opposing and equal reaction. If you want to move, you must overcome friction and gravity. This may not seem to be a good state of affairs, until you realise that it is actually the opposition of gravity and friction that strengthens you. In order for you to walk and jump, your muscles have to develop the strength to overcome gravity and friction.
The experience of astronauts shows that when they go to outer space where there is less gravity and friction, their muscles and bones actually become weaker, to an extent where some fail to walk for some time on their return to earth. Without the opposition of gravity and friction their bones and muscles deteriorate.
personal challenges
Just a few days ago, I came across some resistance myself. I got an anonymous message posted from the comment page on my website. Usually these messages are from people that have found my articles and website interesting and helpful and they encourage me greatly to keep writing and telling people that they can achieve their dreams. However, this message was different. The unknown person accused me of stealing their work word for word in my articles.
I was shocked, to say the least. More surprising was the fact that he went on to threaten to “notify the Post and even take a large ad in the Times and Daily to expose” me. I read the message again just to be sure I was reading it correctly. I was.

What I felt at the time was a little disappointment and then amusement. This soon turned to utter disbelief when a few minutes later the anonymous writer sent an email declaring his identity and formally accusing me that “most of the articles that you have written for the Post contain my original work and writing.” It was from someone I truly respect and admire, and someone I aspired to work very closely with in future in order to make a positive difference to the lives of many people in this country.
the resolve to overcome
However, my disappointment, disbelief and amusement soon turned into a burning resolve not only to continue doing what I am doing, but to do it even better. In addition to that I was inspired to do a lot more than I am currently. That resistance and opposition is perhaps the very thing I needed to strengthen myself and develop myself further. I refuse to wallow in fear and let anything like that hinder me. This will not be the stone that will crush me, but the stepping stone to greater things!
I subscribe to Stephen R. Covey’s philosophy that “Opposition is a natural part of life. Just as we develop our physical muscles through overcoming opposition - such as lifting weights - we develop our character muscles by overcoming challenges and adversity.”
welcome challenges
So, if you are not being challenged in any way, you cannot grow. If you do not have anything to push against, you cannot make any progress. This is a revealing but true concept. If you are absolutely satisfied with your life the truth remains that you will not try to change it in any way. Any positive change must come as a result of some negative influence that forces you to change.
This negative influence can take many forms - from dissatisfaction with your work to disappointment from your girlfriend or boyfriend. There are many geniuses out there who found their passion and did amazing things after some tragic event in their lives or after being disappointed in one way or another.
be prepared for it
As a dreamer, you must always be prepared for opposition. In particular, you must be prepared for the nay-sayers and the haters. These are the people that would love to see you fail and they know that you will fail in trying to live the life that you deserve. At times it may be people you truly trust to help you along on your journey. Instead they try to stop you and discourage you. Spouses, relatives and close friends are some examples. My anonymous e-mailer is another.
This is a facet of human nature that is hard to understand. Why would anyone want to stop someone else from being all that they can be? The answer is simple. That would expose their own failures and shortcomings. It is not that they don’t believe in you – they just don’t have enough belief in themselves. They would judge you based on their own abilities. But rather than get discouraged and defeated you can use their unbelief to spur you on. I have found that there is nothing that can encourage you to take action more than having someone show doubt in what you can do.
looking forward
One of my favourite motivational speakers, Jim Rohn, tells a story of how his former boss did not believe in his abilities and thought he was a failure. When Jim became wealthy from his speaking business he took a briefcase full of dollar bills, got into his former boss’s office, opened the briefcase, poured all the dollar bills on the desk in front of where the guy was seated and exclaimed just two words before walking out – “count it!”
As Lee Iacocca said: “In times of great stress or adversity it's always best to keep busy, to plow your anger and your energy into something positive.” What Jim Rohn did is a good example of that principle at work. I would urge you right now to write a list of things people in the past have said you can’t do. I would urge you also to plan your victory celebration – what are you going to do once you get there? What are you going to do to help elevate those who will be in the position you may be in now?
conclusion
The Bible says in Genesis as Joseph addressed his brothers: “But as for you, ye thought evil against me; but God meant it unto good…” Turn the negativity into a positive. Overcome the opposition and prove them wrong.
You are all you can be. Go on and be it.

LINK: https://www.motivation-for-dreamers.com/negativity.html"

</string>
    <string name="article3">
"Does it seem like despite your best efforts things never work out as you planned? Are you in despair because just when it seems you are making progress something goes wrong? At such times it is easy to feel defeated and to give up, but what can you do to stay on top of things?
It is a fact of life that despite all your best efforts at planning, strategizing and being careful not to make mistakes some things will go wrong sometimes. One of my favorite poems, “Don’t Quit,” makes the statement more eloquently by saying:
When things go wrong, as they sometimes will
When the road you’re trudging seems all uphill…
…Rest if you must, but don’t you quit.
I have seen this poem in countless places, mostly in the rooms of many a college or university student. It is a source of strength and hope for many during difficult and stressful times. The reason is that it states a simple truth so well that for many it is like shining a light in the darkness.
I stuck it on my university room wall at one point. The reason for putting it on the wall is simple. When things are going wrong it is very easy to lose perspective and to focus on the problem. The light in our lives often goes off at such instances. The message on the wall is like a light shining in the darkness demanding our attention. It is a reminder that no matter how bad it may seem, there is always hope. At such times, often after failing a test or just being so overwhelmed with schoolwork, it would be a great source of hope and encouragement.
things don’t always go as planned
Things will go wrong at times, but you determine what happens after a setback. There are in essence two basic mindsets when it comes to dealing with setbacks. One is the mindset of a pessimist and the other is one of an optimist. Dr. Seligman in the book “Learned Optimism” states that there are some differences in the way a pessimist and an optimist view a problem. His explanation gives a lot of insight as to why some people manage to overcome setbacks and difficulties and others spiral into a dungeon of defeat and self doubt.
the optimistic versus the pessimistic view
The first is that the optimist will see a setback as being temporary, whereas the pessimist will view it as permanent. The saying goes “never make a permanent decision based on temporary circumstances.” The pessimist will do just that. Rather than recognise the problem as being confined in time and able to be resolved they see it as insurmountable and lasting. The optimist will see the event as being limited in time with little or no real impact on the future.
The second difference is how the pessimist and the optimist will view a setback in terms of scope and effect. The pessimist tends to regard a bad event or outcome as being pervasive and affecting everything around them. Just because they made a loss on one business decision they will feel that their entire business is not working and a bad investment, when the truth is that only one deal went wrong. The optimist is able to isolate a bad event and its effects and to treat it as just a bad event that does not affect everything else in their life.

Thirdly, the pessimist will view a setback as having an internal or personal origin. A bad turn of events is regarded by such a person as having been caused by some flaw or shortcoming in their own character. The optimist takes the healthy view that the event is external to them and not necessarily caused by them. They realise that there is probably nothing they could have done personally to prevent what happened from happening. Learning to detach yourself from problems and setbacks is a skill that is essential to achieving success and your dreams. Clarity of mind cannot be there if you see yourself as part of the problem. Without clarity of mind you will not overcome the setback easily.
the important lesson
Fourthly, and most importantly, the optimist knows that, although they had no control over what happened, they have the power to influence or determine the outcome. This is what determines whether you rise again after you fall or stay on your belly and mourn endlessly until you are blue in the face.
attitude matters
Your attitude when things go wrong is ultimately more important than the event itself and is what will determine if the outcome will be positive or negative. I am in agreement with Kahlil Gibran when he says that “Your living is determined not so much by what life brings to you as by the attitude you bring to life; not so much by what happens to you as by the way your mind looks at what happens.
If you have been defeated by a negative attitude towards setbacks do not lose hope. Admitting your mistakes is the first step to correcting them. A positive attitude can be learnt and developed. It is a matter of choice. You can make the choice, whenever faced with a difficulty to look at it form an optimistic point of view rather than a pessimistic one.
there’s always a silver lining
It is often said that “every adversity has within it the seeds of an equivalent or greater benefit.” Whenever you are faced with a setback ask yourself what you could do to turn it around. Better still, ask yourself how you can benefit from the setback. It may sound ridiculous, but you can benefit from a setback if you change your perspective. You will realise that there is nothing so bad you cannot use it for some good and that there is no situation that is totally hopeless. I have had many times when I have turned a “bad” situation into one that benefits me. It’s a matter of attitude.
conclusion
Take the advice from “Don’t Quit” and remember that:
“Success is failure turned inside out,
The silver tint of the clouds of doubt,
And you can never tell how close you are,
It may be near when it seems so far;
So stick to the fight when you're hardest hit,
It's when things seem worst
That you must not quit.
You are all you can be. Go on and be it.
LINK: https://www.motivation-for-dreamers.com/never-quit.html"
</string>
    <string name="article4">"What exactly are you capable of achieving? What is a realistic expectation for your life and what constitutes sheer madness? Is there a limit to how high you should aim?
The simple answer to these questions is simply that you are capable of achieving anything you set your mind to; if you can think it, then it’s a realistic expectation; and you can aim as high as you want.
the sky has never been the limit
We have probably all heard the “wise” saying: “the sky is the limit.” This would seem to have a lot of wisdom in it at first glance. However, it implies that man’s potential has a limit when in actual fact, man’s potential is limitless. Let’s examine what exactly your potential as a human being is.
Firstly, let’s define potential. Potential is all that you can be, but have not yet become. It is all you can accomplish, but have not yet accomplished. It is unexposed or dormant ability.
This means that the ability to become and to do is already there. It just hasn’t been brought out and utilized.
Consider a fertilized human egg (zygote). That single cell has the ability to form every part of the human body. Everything from your brain to your toenails can be formed by that single cell. It has unlimited potential.
your potential is limitless
Similarly, the mind of man has unlimited potential. It has the limitless ability to create. Man has been on earth for thousands of years, yet we are still making new discoveries today and creating new things everyday. We cannot exhaust the creative power of our minds.
The functioning of our minds remains, for the most part, a mystery even to modern day science. But even though we do not understand it’s functioning, we cannot deny its power.

you have the power within
Your most powerful asset is your mind. The answer to the question ‘what is a realistic goal and what is achievable’ is entirely up to you. If your mind can accept that something is achievable, it will find a way to attain that thing.
“Whatever the mind of man can conceive and believe, it can achieve.” These are the immortal words of Napoleon Hill, a man who truly understood that “there are no limitations to the mind except those we acknowledge.”
Your possibilities are limited only by your thinking. What may be a limit for one person is a walk in the park for another. It’s all in the mindset.
Your potential as a human being, then, is unlimited. You have within you the ability to become and to achieve anything you want. Now that you understand that your potential is limitless, your next challenge is to answer the question: what do you want out of life?
think of the possibilities
Before you start scratching your head and making excuses, let me help you a little. If money, education, social status and so on, were no hindrance what would you want out of life? If all the knowledge and wealth in the world were at your disposal what would you want to be and to do?
Even with all the resources at your disposal, it is very likely that you would still struggle to come up with 3 goals that you are absolutely passionate about and to which you would dedicate every waking hour. Therein lies the problem – it is not your possibilities that are limited, it is your thinking!
Your vision is limited only by you. The problem is that you don’t know what you should be. It’s not your fault, really: your education has messed you up. It has taken your boundless potential and shrunk it and shaped it into a narrow title. You are a “nurse”, or “accountant” or “driver”.
It doesn’t matter what title has been placed on you, you need to break free from it. You are not what you do. See yourself as the truly capable human being that you are.
cultivate the right mindset
This requires that you look deep within and examine your mindset. Are there things you have accepted simply because everyone else seems to accept them? Have you accepted society’s standards as your own?
A word of caution: society celebrates mediocrity. Ordinary people do not like it when others get ahead. It only exposes their lack of vision and motivation. That is why mediocrity is often embraced and excellence is shunned. Being ordinary is acceptable.
If you want more, there is something wrong with you.If something is widely accepted and everyone is doing it, it is probably better for you as a dreamer not to do it. If you want to get what everyone else is getting, do what everyone else is doing.
It is not difficult to see the results others are getting from what they are doing. The good news is you don’t have to do what they are doing. Find your own way. Utilise the potential within you.
Dig out your potential like a prospector digs for oil. The oil has always been there just waiting to be tapped. But if no one bothered to search for it and bring it to the surface it would just remain there dormant, wasting and useless.
So it is with your potential. If you do not challenge yourself to grow beyond your present circumstances, it will just waste away and be totally useless not only to you, but to the rest of humanity.
conclusion
Do not rob this country of such a great resource as yourself. Utilise your potential. Be all that you can be so that when you die, you will have utilized every single drop of your being.
Marianne Williamson said – “Our deepest fear is not that we are inadequate. Our deepest fear is that we are powerful beyond measure. It is our light, not our darkness, that most frightens us. We ask ourselves, who am I to be brilliant, gorgeous, talented and fabulous? Actually, who are you not to be?”
You are all you can be. Go on and be it.
LINK: https://www.motivation-for-dreamers.com/motivation-myth.html"

</string>
    <string name="article5">"Is there more at stake to the choices you make than just your future? Could you be living a life that is not of your own making? These were the questions that raced through my mind one very ordinary looking day. It turned out to be a mind-opening day.
I was having breakfast in a restaurant on a recent working trip. The waiter greeted me warmly as I went to serve myself. He then retreated to a corner of the room, taking on the common stance that waiters assume with their hands clasped in front, a towel dangling between them.
As I sat down to eat he came and asked whether I needed some coffee or tea. Not being particularly fond of hot drinks I declined and said the juice would suffice. He noticed that my glass was small and offered to bring a larger glass of juice.
So the morning went on. He would serve me, then go back to the corner and watch. It was as though at every moment he was observing me and asking himself what else he could do to make my breakfast better and my stay more comfortable.
I got drawn in by all this and also started to observe him. He was humble, quiet, almost making an effort not to be noticed as he stood in that corner. His manner seemed to suggest that he was not important at that point, the customers were.
The generations before
As I stared at him standing in that corner I was drawn back in time. I remembered that my own grandfather had worked in a hotel. He was not a waiter and I can’t remember exactly what he did there, but it suddenly dawned on me that he might have been in a similar situation – catering to customers’ needs in the hotel.
Wow, I thought, what a change of roles. I mean, there was my grandfather working in a hotel some decades ago and doing what he could to support his family and make a better life for his children. Now, here I was, two generations later, sitting in a similar hotel and being waited on by someone.
It struck me that my being in the position was a result, one way or another, of the sacrifice, dedication, love and commitment of my grandfather to his wife and his children. It wasn’t just him though, but everyone else that came before me. My grandparents raised up my parents, who raised me. Where would I be had they all not done their part?
turning the tables
I also wondered as I watched the waiter what he was thinking. Was he thinking about staying in a hotel some day and also being waited on by someone? Did he ever dream of being on the other side of the situation? What were his hopes and dreams for the future? I don’t know, but I wanted to tell him that he could have any future he wanted for himself. I wanted to tell him that he could get to the other side. It is more likely, though, that he was thinking about his family and what he could do to provide for them right there and then by working in that hotel.
As for my grandfather, he did turn the tables and move to the other side of the equation. How? Through my parents, through me, and through everyone of my family members that have a better life today because he worked hard. Whatever kind of life we have today, he contributed to it. The success or failure of any one generation is influenced by the success or failure of the preceding generations.

I realised at that moment that we carry the dreams and hopes of the generations before us. What parent does not wish his children to have a better life than he has, no matter how good it is? Would my grandfather not feel a sense of accomplishment to see his own children and grandchildren being able to afford to stay in a hotel and have the finer things in life? Would he not feel a sense of failure to see them suffering and struggling through life two generations after him?
remember the sacrifices made
Remember the sacrifice and dedication shown to you by those that walked before you. Remember everyday as you make your choices in life that you carry their hopes and dreams on your shoulders. They have done what they could to make things better for you and to give you what you need to succeed. Will you make them proud or let them down? Are you building on the foundation they established or are you destroying the hard labour of their hands. Remember the generations past.
passing on the torch
At the same time, I realised that we carry the seed of prosperity for the generations to come after us. What you do and the choices you make will influence the kind of life your children and grandchildren will have. Your life is not really your own. Many others are affected by it.
Prosperity does not refer here to simply financial well-being. There is more to it than that. Imparting the right values, knowledge, attitudes and beliefs is all part of contributing to the prosperity of the generations after you. After all, you can leave your children an inheritance of millions of dollars, but if you have not taught them the right attitude towards money or given them the knowledge of using it well, they will lose it all in a short time, or worse still kill themselves with the excesses of life. The Bible advises that we “Remember the days of old, consider the years of many generations: ask thy father, and he will show thee; thy elders, and they will tell thee.” Wisdom is a treasure to be passed on.
turning the bad to good
There are those of you out there for whom the past generations have been a disappointment and have passed on a torch to you that was nearly burned out. They could perhaps have done better and made things a lot easier for you. Realise, though, that you still have the power to turn things around. Your parents’ failures do not have to be your failures. Neither do you have to suffer the consequences of their mistakes forever. You have the opportunity now to make things better for those that will be after you.
conclusion
Henry Ward Beecher advises that “We should so live and labor in our times that what came to us as seed may go to the next generation as blossom, and what came to us as blossom may go to them as fruit. This expresses the true spirit in the love of mankind.” As the torch handed to us by our forefathers burns in our hands we should endeavour to hand it to the next generation burning even brighter.
You are all you can be. Go on and be it.
LINK: https://www.motivation-for-dreamers.com/past-and-future.html"

</string>
    <string name="article6">"Do you know what is driving you? Why are you working so hard and doing so much to get what you want? Do you know your purpose for being here?
Whatever your dreams may be and whatever you want to achieve, it is important to analyse the reasons for those things. The reasons for what you want to have and to achieve are your why. Your why is intimately tied to your purpose in life.
 the reasons for achievement
It seems strange that most of the time we wonder through life without any real purpose of our own. At times we do achieve great things and have the appearance of having a wonderful life. We may even have every material thing we could ever want and be successful at our careers, businesses and every thing else. But, as many who have achieved success will tell you, you can still feel empty inside and your life can still lack real meaning.
Imagine, for a moment, that you have achieved your dreams. You are famous. So what? You have lots of luxury cars. So what? You are number one in your area of expertise. So what? You have the biggest or best company in the country. So what? You are wealthy beyond your wildest dreams. So what?
Achievement, wealth and recognition in themselves are useless if they do not answer the why question. Why? Because the reason for doing something is ultimately more important than what is done.
everything has a purpose in life
Everything has a purpose in life. The trees, ants, bees, birds and every living thing have a purpose for being. Each plays its own little part in the delicate architecture of life. Every good invention or good tool answers a question. Technology answers the why question – it’s an answer to someone’s problem.

Human beings, whatever you believe their origin to be, are the greatest of all of nature’s wonders. Why are most of them so purposeless in their existence? The Roman emperor and philosopher Marcus Aurelius asks: Everything, a horse, a vine, is created for some duty...For what task, then, were you yourself created?
A substantial number of us exist simply to exist. We live year in and year out as though living itself is our ultimate goal. If we make enough money and have enough things to get us through to the next year we are satisfied. Surely, there is more to our lives than that? How can something so wonderfully made and endowed with potential as you are simply be here to just exist? What is your contribution to the world? Is your being here making any difference to anyone?
the why factor
The answer to these questions lies partly in your why. Your why is the strong reason you desire something. It is not what you desire, but the strong reason why you desire it. If you examine it further you will find that your why is closely tied to your purpose in life: the thing that you are here to do.
So who determines your why and your purpose? Very simply – you do. George Bernard Shaw said This is the true joy in life, the being used for a purpose recognized by yourself as a mighty one. Trouble is, if you are anything like most people you are probably waiting for some miraculous experience that will tell you why you are here and what you must do. Such moments do occur for some people, but they are the exception and not the rule. The fact is, most people already have the starting point for knowing their purpose in life.
It may be something that interests you, excites you, inspires you, or just that small voice in the back of your head that tells you you ought to be doing something. These are often the clues that hold the answer to finding your purpose. Unfortunately, they are often the clues we tend to ignore or suppress. Yes, they may not be complete clues. Certain pieces of the puzzle may be missing. But these pieces can only be found once we decide to set off on the journey.
decision is always the starting point
What is the starting point of that journey? As with most things in life, it is decision. Decide that there is purpose to your life. Then decide to commit yourself to finding your purpose. Without these two decisions being settled in your mind you will wonder through life like 97% of everybody else out there: busy achieving nothing.
Deciding to find your purpose will set you on the right track and make your mind receptive and ready to see every day things in a new light. However, you have to seek out the answers. Read books that make you think, watch inspiring movies, spend time with the right people, develop your interests and passions and, most importantly, read your Bible. All this is part of keeping your mind in the right environment, an environment that is right for revelation and inspiration.
simplicity is often the answer
There is no way in the world anyone can do what I have just described to you and end up living a meaningless life. One piece at a time the puzzle will become clear and complete. You will discover your purpose, and when you do, it will likely not be some experience where you got hit on the head and nearly knocked out by the revelation. It will come naturally. It will be something that combines most of your life’s experiences and your abilities into one perfect purpose. It will be something you probably had a clue about all along.
However, don’t ever make the mistake of wanting to know everything before you start anything. Start where you are with what you have and what you know. Would you dare write a novel without first learning the alphabet? Take the first steps and you will be on your way. If you follow the process you will mature into the person you are meant to be. You will fulfill your purpose, one little step and one little piece at a time.
conclusion
Leo Buscaglia stated that It's not enough to have lived. We should be determined to live for something. May I suggest that it be creating joy for others, sharing what we have for the betterment of (man)kind, bringing hope to the lost and love to the lonely.
You are all you can be. Go on and be it
LINK: https://www.motivation-for-dreamers.com/finding-your-purpose.html"
</string>
    <string name="article7">"Are you busy looking for success everywhere except the one place you can truly find it? Does life seem like a futile chasing after the rainbow?
One possible reason for this could be that you are not looking for success in the right place. It is not in the environment around us or the circumstances we face that we find success, but in ourselves.
The simple fact is that if you are successful within, in your mind, you will be successful on the outside as well. It may seem too simple thing, but it is something we often forget when the pressures of life surround and overwhelm us. When it comes to making everyday choices it usually does not occur to us.
Like I have said before, your mind is your greatest asset. Like any asset, it needs to be built up and improved continually. Abraham Lincoln said he didn’t “think much of a man who is not wiser today than he was yesterday.” He realised the basic truth that continuous improvement is necessary if one is to be truly successful.
knowledge is a huge asset
Knowledge is a powerful asset. It makes the difference between living in abundance and living in lack. The only difference between the managing director in a company and the maid in the same company is their knowledge. The MD knows something the maid doesn’t. That is why he earns a hundred times more than she does.
It is what you know that will bring you success. It’s what you don’t know that will cause you to fail. Why then, do some get it so wrong? For example many people look for promotions without acquiring the necessary skills and knowledge they need to be promoted. Many business people are struggling because they just won’t take the time to learn about accounting, marketing and all that goes with doing business. That’s like trying to drive a car without first putting in the fuel.

the three percent rule
“Here is a rule that will guarantee your success – and possibly make you rich: Invest 3 percent of your income back into yourself.” That’s great advice from Brian Tracy. Investing in yourself can double or triple your income. It will work for you whether you are employed or in business.
James Attucher of the Financial Times agrees with this advice when he says “The only real way I know to triple your money is to invest in yourself.” He goes on to say that you should invest in your own ideas and your own business. But apart from that you should also invest in your mind.
ways to invest in you
There are many ways to invest in yourself. One way is to make it a habit to buy books regularly. Not just any books, of-course, but books that will challenge you and from which you can learn something. Biographies of other successful people, “how-to” books, self-improvement books and professional books such as accounting or public speaking books are examples.
Investing your time and money in learning things such as goal-setting, how to manage your time, how to be more confident and less doubtful, how to be a better speaker, how to adjust your thinking, create new habits and squash bad ones, how to take care of your health, how to focus and so can greatly improve your results in life.
These days books are not the only way to get knowledge, though. We have video, the internet, seminars and workshops on various subjects and even mentoring and coaching programmes. Even watching the right movies can sometimes teach you a thing or two. My favorite business programme, for example, is The Apprentice. It teaches a lot about entrepreneurship in an entertaining manner. Who would have thought that reality T.V could be so educational?
the value of self-education
The point is that you determine how and what you learn as well as how fast you learn. Self-education is important beyond the classroom. In the real world self-education matters a whole lot more than formal education. There are plenty of people with a formal education that are still struggling. Isaac Asimovfully supported this in saying that “Self-education is, I firmly believe, the only kind of education there is.” A formal education is good, but only as a foundation. The sad part is that many are stuck at the foundation level. They don’t realise that in order to complete the building they need to invest in some self-education.
Therefore, do not be like them, who were referred to by James Allen as being “anxious to improve their own lives, but are unwilling to improve themselves. They therefore remain bound.” Dreamers realise that there is no better way to improve your life than to improve your mind. The biggest room in the world is the room for improvement.
Knowledge, then, is a powerful asset, and one which you should always be seeking to improve and build upon in the pursuit of your dreams. The Proverbs declare that “through wisdom is an house builded; and by understanding it is established: And by knowledge shall the chambers be filled with all precious and pleasant riches.”
conclusion
Become addicted to continuous improvement and increase in your knowledge consistently and constantly. With time, you will inevitably become the person that you desire to be. Then you will no longer have to chase after success. Success will follow you. Your mind will become magnetized to attract success.
You are all you can be. Go on and be it.

LINK:  https://www.motivation-for-dreamers.com/invest-in-yourself.html"

</string>
    <string name="article8">
"Who are you and why are you here? It may seem like a straightforward question. Most would answer by giving their name without giving it much thought. However, on deeper reflection, do you really understand who you are?
Our world today has one great irony that is mind-boggling: the majority of people in the world are trying very hard to conform to what someone else wants them to be. It is often so subtle that we fail to realise that that is what we are doing. As Sarah McLachlan points out: “We’re constantly being told what other people think we are, and that’s why it is so important to know yourself.”
It happens at many levels. For instance, television bombards us with images of how we should look and dress, what we should eat and drink, what car we should drive and even what kind of person we should marry. Some even go as far as telling us how to fall in love!
We look around us for things that will help us define who we are. In-fact the majority of people have no sense of identity apart from the clothes they wear, the car they drive, where they live, who they are married to and so on.
If we had to strip you of everything you own and leave you on some island away from everything you think defines you, would you still have a clear sense of who you are? What defines you?
 images of self
Some would think of themselves in terms of their body. The image of their face and body defines who they are. If we were to remove you from your body, would you still know who you are? It sounds weird, I know, but understand that man is a spirit; he lives in a body and has a soul. Your body is simply a means of expressing yourself and interacting with your physical environment.
So your body is not really who you are. At the core of it, you are more than that. In-fact that is why it is so hard for people to fully understand and appreciate who they are. Who you are cannot be seen, touched, smelt, heard or tasted. Your senses cannot tell you who you are.

The concept of self in the true form is something beyond the grasp of our physical bodies and senses. We are complex beings. We cannot be defined by the things around us, but by the things within us. I believe that in essence we are what we think. Physically as human beings we are all essentially the same. It is our thoughts and experiences that differentiate us.
your true identity
Our true identity, then, lies within us, not outside of us. We should define who we are based on our thoughts, our values, principles and beliefs. It’s okay to have material things and all, but they should not be our sense of self. They are just things that are there to make our lives easier. If you were suddenly homeless today that would not change who you are as a person. You would still be you.
What is the importance of all this, you might ask? Ralph Waldo Emerson warns that “The greatest difficulty is that men do not think enough of themselves, do not consider what it is that they are sacrificing when they follow in a herd, or when they cater for their establishment.” So you are sacrificing something when you go through life blindly conforming to everything. You sacrifice your true potential and purpose, which you can only fulfill when you truly understand yourself.
the answer lies within
Look within yourself, not without. For everything begins and ends with your thoughts. Sidney J. Harris adds that “Ninety percent of the world's woe comes from people not knowing themselves, their abilities, their frailties, and even their real virtues. Most of us go almost all the way through life as complete strangers to ourselves.”
It may seem like an overstatement, but it is so. Many lack an understanding of who they are, without which they are unable to know what they care capable of achieving in life. In the days of slavery in Europe and America this was well understood. Black people were forced to change their names to Western names so they would not remember who they really were.
Furthermore, they were banned from knowing how to read or write. That should make the lights flash in someone’s head. The reason this was done was that their masters knew that if they knew how to read they would discover many things, not only about the world around them, but about themselves. Their minds would be stretched to new levels of understanding.
the road to self discovery
Reading is a powerful means of discovering who you really are. If you read the right books and other material you will gain a deeper understanding of others as well as yourself. Unfortunately, there are many who are in a self-imposed prison of ignorance even today. The books are all around them. They just don’t want to read. The culture of reading is not well established in many Zambians. For such people Atwood H. Townsend has some timely advice: “No matter how busy you may think you are, you must find time for reading, or surrender yourself to self-chosen ignorance.”
conclusion
Choose not to live in ignorance about who you are and what you can do. Decide today to discover more about yourself and to start on the journey of self discovery. My best recommendation – read your Bible. Without it, you may never know who you really are.
In the words of James Allen, “Only by much searching and mining are gold and diamonds obtained, and man can find every truth connected with his being if he will dig deep into the mine of his soul.”
You are all you can be. Go on and be it.
LONK:  https://www.motivation-for-dreamers.com/the-real-you.html"

</string>
    <string name="article9">"Are you unhappy when others are succeeding? Does your success seem dependent on someone else’s failure?
“Keeping up with the Joneses” is an expression that is commonly used to describe the attitude of always wanting to keep up with the neighbours in terms of possessions and wanting to have the things that our neighbours have.
Envy is another word that can be used to describe this frame of mind. This is a very appropriate word because it encompasses greed, jealousy, resentment and a strong desire for something somebody else has, usually at whatever cost.
 origins
Unfortunately, it is an attitude that is widespread, not only in Zambia, but all over the world. Throughout our childhood and most of our adult life, competition is the order of the day. Right from our school days we are taught that our self worth is measured in relation to other people.
At school, our grading system gives you a number at the end of the term. If you “pass number one” that means you are the best in your class. If you “pass number 25” that means there are 24 other kids that are better than you are. So if you want to be number one and “win” you must make sure that all the other kids “lose” and pass number two or more.
Wait a minute though, why can’t all the kids in class pass number one? Why must we compare one child to another? A simple pass or fail remark on the report card might be sufficient without necessarily stating numbers. Unfortunately for children, parents take these numbers very seriously.
This carries on through life. The boss must ensure that he does not allow his juniors to get too much knowledge or qualifications if he is to keep his number one spot as the top dog in the company. In fact, at times he must deliberately frustrate any efforts by his subordinates to progress.
Even amongst friends and relatives this occurs. Sibling rivalry does not always end when children grow up. A lot of times it continues. The success of one child in adulthood is measured against the success of another. It seems whatever we have achieved seems insignificant when compared to what so and so has done or acquired.



 dangers of the loser mentality
There are several reasons why envy is such a problem. Firstly, if you are envious of another person’s success that means you will never be satisfied with anything you ever achieve. The fact remains that most times there will always be someone that does better than you in some area.
Secondly, if you are envious of other people’s success it means you have no clue what you want for your own life. Just because the Joneses have it or do this and that does not mean you should have it or do it. Will it help you in achieving your own objectives and “minding your own business?” If you have a clear vision for your life, what another person achieves or acquires won’t matter: you will know exactly where you are, why you are there, where you need to go and what you need to do to get there.
Thirdly, carried to some extremes, envious people will even try to cripple the progress of others and stop it if possible. Rather than channel their energy into their own success they channel it into this very unproductive mindset: backstabbing, sabotaging, destroying at every chance they get and spending their prime time on thinking about others instead of thinking of ways to improve their own situation.
 the three basic mindsets
When it comes to succeeding in life there are three basics mindsets that people tend to have. These are the win/lose mentality, the lose/lose mentality and the win/win mentality.
People with a win/lose mentality would be those that compare themselves to other people all the time. They believe that in order for them to succeed others must fail. To them, success is relative.
Those with a lose/lose mentality believe that they can never achieve anything worthwhile so why should they let you do so. They try to keep other people in the sinking boat that they are in. Negativity is the order of the day for them. Don’t ever try to tell such people that you have great plans for your life – they will only criticize you and tell you it can’t be done. After all, they tried that already and it did not work!
Dreamers, who are achievers, have the win/win mentality. Not only do they know that they are capable of and will succeed, but they realise that their success does not depend on other people’s failure. To the contrary, their success depends on other people’s success.
 cultivate it
If you are to succeed in life and become the person you are meant to be, then you must know that you will not get there alone. Therefore you must help others to succeed and to become great if you are to be great yourself. It is often said that the greatest people are always those that help others.
Learn to be happy about others’ success and look forward to your own success. Do not judge yourself based on what others have achieved, but rather based on what you want to achieve. Depending on what you want in life, their success could be failure to you or vice versa, but it should not matter to you either way.
Life is not a race against other people. It is a one man race. You determine the destination, the route, the time limits and the prize. We are all running a different race. How do you compete with someone that is not on the same track as you are?
Envy and jealousy are habits you must always be weary of and stay clear of. Like other bad habits they will only rob you of your energy, creativity, drive, clarity of mind and enthusiasm for life.
conclusion
Stephen R. Covey, in discussing this subject states: “Win/win is based on the paradigm that there is plenty for everybody, that one person’s success is not achieved at the expense or exclusion of the success of others…It’s not your way or my way; it’s a better way, a higher way.”
You are all you can be. Go on and be it.

LINK:  https://www.motivation-for-dreamers.com/winning-mindset.html"

</string>
    <string name="article10">
"Turn off the T.V. Turn down the volume on your radio. Block out all noise. Be quiet and listen. Listen for just five minutes. I don’t want you to pay attention for my sake, but for yours. Are you not worth five minutes of your own time?
Do you have a deep desire to achieve something great? Do you want to live a more satisfying life? Can you see yourself being happy and successful in every way? Do you believe in your own potential and that here is much more to you than meets the eye?
If so, you are a dreamer. This article is dedicated to you. Right now you are the most important person around. If you had been the only person to ever read this article, I would still have written it, just for you. You are that special.
what is a dreamer?
But before we go any further, let me qualify what a dreamer is because people often don’t appreciate being called dreamers. In-fact, it’s almost an insult to call someone a dreamer these days. It’s associated with having your head in the clouds and not being realistic. So let me explain.
A dreamer is a person who is not afraid to challenge society’s norms and not afraid to tread their own path rather than following the well-trodden path. A dreamer is someone who is always willing to take a chance and always asks why before doing something that others are doing blindly. A dreamer is a person who has a great futuristic picture which they work to achieve at all costs. Dreamers are world changers.
Dreamers chart their own course and destiny. Dreamers are always striving to be the person they were meant to be and are not afraid to be different. I believe every one of us is born unique in every way, but over the years we work very hard to become like everyone else.
Do not follow the crowd
Society’s commonsense tells us that that is the way to go. Unfortunately, commonsense is not always good-sense. It’s just common. If you are a dreamer you cannot afford to work on society’s assumptions and standards. You have to be unique.
For instance, a lot of people have spent anything from 15 to 20 years getting an education so they can have that perfect job and earn a huge salary. Unfortunately for most, the perfect job and the huge earnings never materialize. They only have the long hard years of work and loads of papers with unpronounceable names to show for it.

Most of them have lost touch with the very people they are working so hard to provide for - their husband, wife and children, all because of having to “work hard” for a living. Yet few ask themselves if there is a better way. They blindly follow what they’ve always been taught.
chart your own course
I am here to tell you that there is another way. It’s not for everyone. It’s not the only way. It’s not the easier way. Actually, it is more likely to be the harder way. But I guarantee you it is the best way. It is simply this – follow your dreams. If you can think it, you can have it.
Following your dreams, however, is a process and comes at a price. What is the process and what is the price to be paid? Be patient. All will be revealed. Patience, by the way is part of it. Get-rich-quick and easy success schemes don’t last.
- What's in store?
Over the coming weeks I will talk about the characteristics of a dreamer and some of the things you absolutely must do if you want to live the life you deserve to live. Some of them you may already know and others will be new. Whatever the case, you will pick up a number of useful ideas that may just make the difference between living in mediocrity and living a fulfilled life.
Brian Tracy states that “all successful men and women are big dreamers. They imagine what their future could be, ideal in every respect, and then they work every day toward their distant vision, that goal or purpose.”
If you are not a dreamer I urge you to watch this space every week. It may shed light into the darkness in your life. Together, we can find answers to some of life’s questions, but YOU have to do the searching.
I can help
I have struggled with and continue to struggle with many of life’s questions myself. These struggles have led me to some startling and amazing discoveries about human potential, achievement, motivation, success and living your dreams.
I have a curiosity about life and see lessons on success and achievement in the most ordinary of events or places. I want to share what I have learnt with you. I can't promise you that you will achieve your dreams after reading my articles - that is entirely up to you and no one else. However, what I will share with you will immensely help you in your desire to live the life you want and deserve.
It is a marvel to think what would happen to Zambia if the dreamers woke up and did something about their dreams. This country would never be the same. But there is hope and it starts with each and every one of us making a difference in our own lives. You have no idea what impact a single person’s dream can have on an entire nation.
conclusion
I hope your dream will come to life and make a positive contribution to the lives of the people of this beautiful country. You can make all the difference and, if you are a dreamer, I know you are not waiting for someone else to do it. You do it!
Sadly but true, and in the words of Myles Munroe - “The poorest man in the world is the man without a dream. The most frustrated man in the world is the man with a dream that never becomes reality."
</string>
    <string name="mypara">"As we know that the stress has increased in our society, which leads to many severe health problems like Heart disease, Obesity, Depression and anxiety. This is also the main reason for attempting suicides. Therefore, We are making android app and website (www.firstloveyourself.co.in) that will motivate and guide people to live a stress free life. Our Application will contain the following features:
•         Motivational and Humorous  Contents (Videos, Articles): This will contain the videos and Articles of real life stories that can help to motivate the peoples. It will also contain some Humorous content too.
•         Chat: In this feature users can chat and share their problems with each other.
•         Counselors: This feature will help the peoples to chat with Counselors and if they like them then they can set an appointment.(COMING SOON…)
•         Explore The Nature: In this feature we will show the peoples the nature’s best place to visit so they can see how beautiful the life and nature is.
•         Events: This feature will contain all the lively events so where they can book the event and enjoy it.

This is the Pre-Beta version of our original work and we would be glad for your feedbacks(Can send as many you like).
                            THANK YOU!!!
"</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="the_worthy">The Worthy</string>
    <string name="loss">Loss</string>
    <string name="lets_go">Lets Go</string>
    <string name="legacy">Legacy</string>
    <string name="made_for_this">Made For This</string>
    <string name="you_will_never_be_a_god">You Will Never Be A God</string>
    <string name="how_to_stop_bullying">How To Stop Bullying</string>
    <string name="a_man_out_of_time">A Man Out Of Time</string>
    <string name="there_was_no_other_way">There Was No Other Way</string>
    <string name="humorous_1">Humorous 1</string>
    <string name="humorous_2">Humorous 2</string>
    <string name="humorous_3">Humorous 3</string>
    <string name="login">Login</string>
    <string name="enter_username">Enter Username</string>
    <string name="enter_password">Enter Password</string>
    <string name="title_activity_videos">videos</string>
    <string name="tab_text_1">Tab 1</string>
    <string name="tab_text_2">Tab 2</string>
</resources>

